Like Diane mentioned, if you don't want to run a lot of AA experiments,
像 Diane 提到过的 如果你不想运行太多的 A/A 实验
you can run one experiment and then use it to estimate the variability of your
你可以运行一次实验 然后使用 Bootstrap 法
metric using something called the Bootstrap Method.
估计指标的差异性
The idea in bootstrapping is that you run one experiment.
bootstrapping 的理念是你运行一次实验
And even though in our spreadsheet we only showed one number from each group,
虽然在表格中 每个实验每一组我们只显示了一个数字
for each experiment, the click-through probability,
它的点击概率
those numbers were actually calculated from a lot of individual data points,
实际上 这些数字是由单独的很多数据点计算得来的
about a bunch of individual page views and clicks.
包括很多的页面浏览量与点击数据
Then you take a random sample of those data points from each
然后你从实验的每一组中
side of the experiment, and calculate the click-through
抽取随机的数据点 并把随机样本视作完整的实验组
probability based on that random sample as if it were a full experimental group.
然后计算点击概率
Then you record the difference in click through probabilities and
你可以记录点击概率的差别
use that as a simulated experiment.
将其视作实验
Then you repeat this process over and over, recording the results.
然后你不断重复这个过程 记录结果
And you can use the results as if you had run multiple experiments,
你可以当作运行了多次实验来运用这些结果
even though you really only ran one big experiment.
虽然你实际上只运行了一个较大的实验
So the numbers in this spreadsheet,
所以表格中的这些数字
we've been assuming that they came from multiple A/A tests.
我们假设它们是来自多次 A/A 测试
But they actually could have come from one big experiment,
但其实它们是来自一次大型实验
from which we drew many bootstrap samples.
我们从中得到了很多 bootstrap 样本
Now it's your turn to calculate confidence intervals empirically.
现在 你要通过实证方法计算置信区间
Follow the link in the instructor's notes to get to this spreadsheet with
通过讲师注释的链接
values of click through probability across 40 experiments.
获取 40 次实验的点击概率值的表格
These could be 40 different A/A tests, or
这个可以是 40 次不同的 A/A 测试
they could be 40 groups sampled using bootstrapping.
也可以是通过 bootstrapping 获得的 40 组样本
The analysis is the same.
分析是一样的
Note that the sample size was 100 users in each group of the experiment.
请注意 这里的样本量是实验每组 100 名用户
For each experiment,
对每次实验
calculate the difference in the click-through-probability between
计算两组间点击概率
the two groups.
的差异
Then calculate a 95% confidence interval in two different ways.
然后用两种不同的方式计算 95% 的置信区间
First, calculate the standard deviation of the differences, and
首先 计算这些差异的标准偏差
then assume that the metric is normally distributed to calculate the width of
假设指标是正态分布的
the confidence interval.
然后计算置信区间的宽度
Use the average of the 40 differences as the point estimate, or
使用 40 组差异的平均值作为点估计
the center of your confidence interval.
或者说置信区间的中心点
Second, calculate an empirical confidence interval Using just
第二 使用这些差异
the differences,
通过实证计算置信区间
not making any assumption about the distribution of the metric.
但不对指标的分布做出假设
You can use Google Spreadsheets or
你可以使用 Google 电子数据表
any other method you want to carry out the calculations.
或其他方式进行计算
Write the upper and lower bounds of your two confidence levels in these boxes to
在方框中写下两个置信度的上限和下限
four decimal places.
精确至小数位后第四位